halfoffdeals.com 2017-05-14

# Serving up 40-90% savings on your favorite local restaurants, spas, and more! | HalfOffDeals

**Privacy Policy Overview:**  
Welcome to the NeoFill � privacy policy. This privacy policy is applicable to your use of our services available from ("NeoFill�") and under the domain and sub-domains of www.HalfOffDeals.com, [www.GoFishDeals.com](http://www.gofishdeals.com/), [www.NeoFillBids.com](http://www.neofillbids.com/)� and BidDestination.com (the "Sites") and the general principles for the websites of our subsidiaries and affiliates.� This policy explains how we use and protect your personal information.� Please read this privacy policy carefully.� By accessing and using our Sites, you acknowledge that you have read, understand and agree to be bound to all of the terms of this privacy policy and our Sites terms of use.� We reserve the right to modify the terms of this Privacy Policy at any time without reason or notice. 

**Information Collection and Use:  
**When you visit and navigate our site, we will not collect any personal information about you unless you provide us that information voluntarily. Personal information includes your name, address, e-mail address, telephone number and/or credit card. NeoFill� collects information from users at several different points on its site and it is the sole owner of the information collected on this site. NeoFill� does not sell, share, or rent this information to others in ways different from what is disclosed in this statement. The NeoFill� site contains links to other sites. NeoFill� is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of websites that link to or from NeoFill�.

**Subscriber ("user") Registration and Order:**  
We request information from the user on our order form or during the registration process.� Here a user must provide contact information (i.e. name, email and address) and financial information (i.e. credit card number, expiration date).   
We use this customer contact information to send information to our registered users about the services for which they have subscribed. We use the financial information collected to verify the user's identity and to bill the user for products and services. 

**Cookies:**  
A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user's hard drive containing information about the user. NeoFill� uses cookies in the certain areas of our site to save users' contact information, so that they don't have to re-enter it each time they visit certain areas of the site. 

**Log Files:**  
We use your IP (Internet Provider) address to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer our website. We use IP addresses to analyze trends and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information.

**Data Sharing:**  
We do not give out, sell or rent registered user address or credit card information without consent except where a) we have your consent b) We provide such information to trusted businesses or persons for the sole purpose of processing personally identifying information on our behalf c) when we need to deliver a product or service that a registered user has ordered or d) to comply with valid legal process. In addition, as a facilitator of online fundraising events, NeoFill� may provide personal information of donors, registered users who place items on their "watchlist" and all bidders to the non-profits involved in the associated auction event. We may occasionally share aggregated non-personally identifiable user demographic information with our partners and advertisers such as anonymous usage data, referring URLs, number of clicks etc. This is not linked to any personal information that can identify an individual person.

We may store and process personal information collected on our site in the United States in which NeoFill� or its affiliates maintain facilities. By using our services, you consent to the transfer of your information among these facilities.

In the event of a transfer of ownership of NeoFill�, such as acquisition by or merger with another company, we will provide notice if you become subject to a different privacy policy.

**Links to Other Websites** :  
This website contains links to other sites. Please be aware that NeoFill� is not responsible for the privacy practices of sites which link to or from NeoFill�. We encourage our users to read the privacy statements of every website they visit that collects personally identifiable information.

**Security** :  
NeoFill� takes every precaution to protect our users' information.� When users submit sensitive information via the website, their information is protected both online and off-line.� When our registration/order form asks users to enter sensitive information (such as credit card number), that information is encrypted and is protected with the best encryption software in the industry " SSL.� While on a secure page, such as our order form, the lock icon on the bottom of Web browsers such as Netscape Navigator and Microsoft Internet Explorer becomes locked, as opposed to un-locked, or open, when you are just "surfing."

**Correspondence With Users**  
We send all registered users on our Auction ecommerce platform (i.e. NeoFillBids.com and BidDestination.com) an email confirming their registration.� We also send site and service announcement updates that contain important information about the services on our website. In addition, our Customer Support Department may, as the individual situation warrants, communicate with users via telephone or email to provide them with services they have requested or to follow-up on issues relating to their account.

When a user registers as a user of NeoFill�, the user agrees to receive communications from NeoFill�. We do not sell, rent or otherwise provide our registered users email addresses to third parties, unless the third party is affiliated with a promotional offer (i.e. Merchant, Media Partner). However we occasionally send emails to our registered users informing them of our new products and services or special promotions. Users who do not wish to receive this correspondence may unsubscribe from receiving such information at any time

**Correcting/Updating Personal Information:**  
Registered users can update their address or credit/debit card information at any time by logging into the My Account area of the site (using their Username and Password) and then clicking edit in the "My Profile" section. 

**Parental Information:**  
At NeoFill� we are aware that many children may want to visit us on the Internet. Although we welcome browsing, we ask that only individuals who are over the age of 18 register on our site. If we learn that we inadvertently have collected identifying personal information from an individual under the age of 18, we will promptly delete that information from our system. 

Contacting Us  
If you have any questions about NeoFill�'s Privacy Policy or the practices of this site, please contact Customer Support via email to [CustomerService@NeoFill.com](mailto:CustomerService@NeoFill.com) or 866.311.9806.

Effective�January 1, 2013
